{
    "subject": "resource/Bye,_See_You_Monday",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Bye, See You Monday",
    "human_readable": "The name of Bye, See You Monday is Bye, See You Monday.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8066524863243103,
            "question": "What kind of work could 'Bye, See You Monday' be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8034408688545227,
            "question": "Does the title 'Bye, See You Monday' give any clues about the content?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22255143523216248,
            "question": "Is the title of this work also its name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13188280165195465,
            "question": "What is the name of the work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04916971176862717,
            "question": "Would you be interested in learning more about this work based on its name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03734491765499115,
            "question": "What is your initial impression based on the title alone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.030632812529802322,
            "question": "Could this title belong to a song, book, or film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.019238397479057312,
            "question": "Does the title suggest a specific tone or mood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01867842860519886,
            "question": "Can you think of any other works with similar titles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.011561799794435501,
            "question": "How does the structure of the title influence its impact?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Bye, See You Monday is Bye, See You Monday.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1707_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you think of any other works with similar titles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1707_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the title suggest a specific tone or mood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1707_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could this title belong to a song, book, or film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1707_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1707_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1707_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1707_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1707_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1707_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1707_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1707_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1707_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1707_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1707_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe document mentions the film \"Bye, See You Monday\" and provides details about its plot and cast. This directly supports the statement that the name of the movie \"Bye, See You Monday\" is indeed \"Bye, See You Monday.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}